Guide to the Committee of 100 on the Federal City records [Part I], 1932-2003 MS2017
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Committee of 100 on the Federal City records [Part I]
1932-1995
Circa 1970 - Circa 1999
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Committee of 100 on the Federal City (Washington, D.C.)
MS2017
50 Linear Feet
Collection contains correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, newspaper articles, memorandum, bank statements, financial records, maps, and blueprints. The material dates from 1932-2003 with the bulk of the material falling within the dates 1950-87. The majority of the documents focus on city planning and transportation issues. These detail the various highway and rapid transit projects facing the district, as well as looking at zoning regulations and legal procedures and the debates and discussions between different committee members on many topics concerning planning issues in the District of Columbia.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
The Committee of 100 on the Federal City donated these records in 1986. Dorn McGrath, former chair of the Committee gave a gift in 1989. A final donation was made by former chair David Grinnel in 1991.
Historical or Biographical Note
The mission of the Committee of 100 on the Federal City is to safeguard and advance the fundamental planning, environmental and aesthetic values inherited from the L'Enfant Plan and the McMillan Commission that give Washington its historic distinction, natural beauty and overall livability. The Committee advances the proposition that planning of the highest caliber is essential to ensure for residents of Washington D.C. - indeed for all the citizens of the United States for whom the Nation's Capital is a symbol - the attainment and preservation of a city worthy of the Nation. From specific proposals such as its plan for the redesign of the Whitehurst Freeway below Georgetown, to more general initiatives, such as testimony on regional air quality standards and support for reinvigorating of the NCPC, the Committee continues its broad campaign for exemplary planning in the Nation's Capital. The Committee is engaging in close consultation on planning issues with the Congress and the District of Columbia Government. The Committee has also established its own ad hoc subcommittee on regional planning to work in liaison with kindred organizations in Maryland and Virginia.
The Committee of 100 on the federal City was organized in 1923 by the American Planning and Civic Association (APCA) in order to study the problems facing the Nation's capital. Frederic A. Delano, Uncle to President Franklin Delano Roosevelt, was the first Chairman of the Committee. Following its conception, the Committee of 100 has served as a citizens forum discussing planning issues that confront the District. The Committee separated itself from the APCA in 1965 and incorporated as a non-profit organization.
For over half a century, the Committee has attracted to its membership architects, planners, landscape architects, lawyers, conservationists, historians, and concerned citizens from diverse professions and backgrounds. It has sought to rally national, regional, and local organizations which share in the mission of safeguarding the heritage of Washington, D.C. Not only is the Committee of 100 on the Federal City the oldest planning body and the oldest citizens' forum on planning issues in the Nation's Capital, it is also one of the most effective and vigorous organizations of its kind.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, newspaper articles, memorandum, bank statements, maps, and blueprints. The material dates from 1932-91 with the bulk of the material falling within the dates 1950-1987.
The majority of the documents focus on city planning and transportation issues. These detail the various highway and rapid transit projects facing the district, as well as looking at zoning regulations and legal procedures and the debates and discussions between different committee members on many topics concerning planning issues in the District of Columbia. Another portion of the collection deals with the founding and governing procedures of the committee including early historical documents. This early history has an history of the committee donated by Eric T. Menke. Significant people included in these records are Peter S. Craig, Frederic Delano, Harlean James, Ulysses Grant III, Dorn Mc Grath, John Nolen Jr., Constance Green, and Polly Shackleton. Some of the more important issues are the Three sisters Bridge Controversy, WMATA projects such as Metro Rail design and planning, the Pennsylvania. Avenue Development Corporation, Cleveland Park Historical Society, Potomac River Conversation, Inner Loop Freeway Planning (I-65 and I-295), Federal Triangle, Old Post Office, parking problems, and building height restrictions.
The collection as a whole provides researchers with information on the founding and organization of the Committee of 100, while showing how it functioned as citizens forum for discussing the great planning issues facing the Nation's Capital.
Collection Organization
Organized into eight series: Organizational history and background, Chronological files, General correspondence, Committee records, Financial records, Subject/Issues files, Oversize records, and Accession 2011.068
Washington (D.C.); Shaw (Washington, D.C.); Federal Triangle (Washington, D.C.); Zoning; Three Sisters Bridge (proposed); Transportation maps; Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority; Transportation; City planning; Roads; Height restrictions; Buildings; Local transit; Shackleton, Polly; Committee of 100 on the Federal City (Washington, D.C.); Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority; Green, Constance McLaughlin; Nolen, John; Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation; McGrath, Dorn Charles; Craig, Peter Stebbins; Delano, Frederic Adrian; United States. Post Office Dept.--Buildings--Washington (D.C.); Grant, U. S. (Ulysses S.), 1881-1968
- Organizational history and background, 1965-1981; MS2017 Series 1
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains articles of incorporation, statements, and reports. These materials cover 1965-81. This series details the structure, activities, and purpose for the Committee of 100. It also provides a brief history of its founding and initial organization.
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Background and History of the "Committee of 100,", 1938-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - By Laws of the Committee of 100, 1965-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Organizational Objectives of the Committee of 100, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Amendment to the Articles of Incorporation, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Chronological files, 1939-1971; MS2017 Series 2
  This series contains pamphlets, correspondence, newspaper articles, and reports. This material dates from 1939-71. The material in this collection was gathered by Eric T. Menke, a long time committee member, in order to detail the history of the Committee of 100.
  - Chronological File, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chronological File, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chronological File, 1945 January-February (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Chronological File, 1945 March-May (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, 1945 June-December (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chronological File, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chronological File, 1947 January (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File, 1947 February-May (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, 1947 September-December (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chronological File, 1948 January-March (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chronological File, 1948 April-December (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 1949 January-May (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chronological File, 1949 June-August (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chronological File, 1949 September-December (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chronological File, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chronological File Index, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chronological File, 1953 January-April (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chronological File, 1953 May-November (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, 1954 January-May (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chronological File, 1954 June-December (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chronological File, 1955 January-June (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File, 1955 July-November (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, 1955 December (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chronological File, 1956 January-February (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 1956 March-June (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chronological File, 1956 July-November (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chronological File, 1956 December (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 1957 January-February (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chronological File, 1957 April-May (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File, 1957 June-December (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chronological File, 1958 January February (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Chronological File, 1958 March (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chronological File, 1958 April (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, 1958 April (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chronological File, 1958 May (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chronological File, 1958 June (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File, 1958 July (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, 1958 August (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Chronological File, 1958 September (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 1958 October (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Chronological File, 1958 November (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Chronological File, 1958 December (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 1959 January (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chronological File, 1959 February (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File, 1959 March (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chronological File, 1959 April (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Chronological File, 1959 May (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chronological File, 1959 June (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, 1959 July (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chronological File, 1959 August (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chronological File, 1959 November (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File, 1959 December (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, 1960 January (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Chronological File, 1960 February (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Chronological File, 1960 March (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Chronological File, 1960 April (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Chronological File, 1960 May (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Chronological File, 1960 June (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Chronological File, 1960 July (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Chronological File, 1960 September (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Chronological File, 1960 October (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Chronological File, 1960 November (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chronological File, 1960 December (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 1961 January (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chronological File, 1961 February (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chronological File, 1961 March-April (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 1961 May-June (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chronological File, 1961 October-November (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File, 1961 December (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Chronological File, 1962 January (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Chronological File, 1962 February (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chronological File, 1962 March (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, 1962 April (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chronological File, 1962 May (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chronological File, 1962 June (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File, 1962 July-September (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, 1962 October-December (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Chronological File, 1963 January (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Chronological File, 1963 February (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Chronological File, 1963 March (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Chronological File, 1963 April (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Chronological File, 1963 May-June (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Chronological File, 1963 July (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Chronological File, 1963 August-October (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Chronological File, 1963 November-December (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Chronological File, 1964 January-February (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Chronological File, 1964 March (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 1964 April (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chronological File, 1964 May (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Chronological File, 1964 June-August (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 1964 September (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chronological File, 1964 October (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File, 1964 November (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Chronological File, 1964 December (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Chronological File, 1965, January-February (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Chronological File, 1965 March (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, 1965 April (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Chronological File, 1965 May-July (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Chronological File, 1965 October (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File, 1965 November-December (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, 1966 January (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Chronological File, 1966 February (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Chronological File, 1966 March (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Chronological File, 1966, March (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Chronological File, 1966 April (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Chronological File, 1966 May (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 1966 June (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Chronological File, 1966 July (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Chronological File, 1966 August (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 1966 September (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Chronological File, 1966 October (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File, 1966 November (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Chronological File, 1966 December (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Chronological File, 1967 January-February (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chronological File, 1967 March-June (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, 1967 July-December (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Chronological File, 1968 January-March (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Chronological File, 1968 April-May (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File, 1968 June-November (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, 1968 December (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Chronological File, 1969 January (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Chronological File, 1969 February-March (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Chronological File, 1969 April (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Chronological File, 1969 May-June (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Chronological File, 1969 July-September (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Chronological File, 1969 October-December (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Chronological File, 1970 January-February (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Chronological File, 1970 March-April (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Chronological File, 1970 May-August (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Chronological File, 1970 September-October (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Chronological File, 1970 November-December (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 1971 January-February (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Chronological File, 1971 March (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Chronological File, 1971 April (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 1971 May-September (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chronological File, 1971 October-November (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File, 1971 December (Box 8, Folder 8)
- General correspondence, 1959-1981; MS2017 Series 3
  This series contains correspondence that dates from 1959-81. Most of the correspondence relates to committee business such as office procedures and personal contact between committee members, and includes invitations and personal responses.
  - General Correspondence, 1959 April (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1980 January-May (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1980 June December (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 January-May (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 June-December (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - General Correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Committee records, 1944-1987; MS2017 Series 4
  The series contains minutes, correspondence, dues cards, and mailing lists. These materials date from 1944-87. The types of records in this series include membership and Trustees. The files with meeting minutes also contain supplemental materials handed out at the meeting. This series also has lists of the general members and Trustees of the Committee.
  Arrangement
  The files are not in alphabetical or chronological order. The folders are in the order that they were in during accession.
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Membership: Correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Dues Cards, A-P, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Membership: Dues Cards, Q-Z, A-F, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Membership: Dues Cards, G-P, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Membership: Dues Cards, Q-Z, A-G, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Membership: Dues Cards, H-Z, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Dues Cards, A-P, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Dues Cards, Q-Z, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Dues Cards, miscellaneous, 1967-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Mailing Lists, 1969-1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Meeting Schedules, 1965-1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1944-1959 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1967 January-June (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1967 July-December (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1971 January-April (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1971 May-December (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1972 January-April (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1972 May-December (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1973 January-April (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1973 May-December (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1980 January-April (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1980 May-December (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1982 January-April (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1982 May-December (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Minutes, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Minutes & Membership, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Rosters, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Stationary of the Committee, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Trustees: Correspondence and Reports, 1965-1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Trustees: Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Trustees: Minutes, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Financial records, 1966-1999; Circa 1970 - Circa 1999; MS2017 Series 5
  This series contains correspondence, checkbooks, bills, receipts, tax forms, and Treasurer's reports. This material dates from 1966-82. The correspondence contains information on legal funds and various project specific fundings. Special highlights include PIPA account details and information concerning Three Sisters Bridge, the Volpe Trial, and other highway projects. Many of the receipts and bills in this series deal with general office tasks such as duplicating and printing services.
  This series is not organized in chronological or alphabetical order. The folders are in the order that they were in when the collection was first accessioned.
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)